freeppttemplates.com 2019-12-13

# FreePPT Templates Privacy

About This Privacy Policy  
Personal Information We Collect  
How Do We Use Your Personal Information?  
Sharing Your Personal Information  
Behavioral Advertising  
Do Not Track  
Your Rights  
Data Retention  
Minors and Children  
Changes  
Contact Us

## About This Privacy Policy

The principal activity of this site is to provide rich content to users of software applications. FreePPTTemplates.com, the site is part of Indezine.com, and we also run several other sites. All our sites respect your privacy. We exist because of you, and this page explains if we collect, store, use and share data. This Privacy Policy document also looks at your right to access, update, restrict, or remove your personal data.

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from FreePPTTemplates, https://www.freeppttemplates.com, or any other subdomains of this domain (the “Site”).

Back

* * *

## Personal Information We Collect

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
  * To get information and control cookies used for tailored advertising from participating companies, see the consumer opt-out pages for the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), or if you're located in the European Union, visit the [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)site. To opt out of Google's display advertising or customize Google Display Network ads, visit the [Google Ads Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
  * To opt out of allowing Google Analytics to use your data for analytics or enrichment, see the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

Back

* * *

## How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
  * Any other reason to make this site and your transaction secure

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

Back

* * *

## Sharing Your Personal Information

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Selz, 2Checkout, and PayPal to power our online store--you can read more about how these services use your Personal Information here:

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can [read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also [opt-out of Google Analytics here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

Back

* * *

## Behavioral Advertising

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

You can opt out of targeted advertising by several of our partner sites:

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

Back

* * *

## Do Not Track

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

Back

* * *

## Your Rights

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the [contact page](https://www.freeppttemplates.com/feedback.html).

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to India and the United States.

Back

* * *

## Data Retention

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

Back

* * *

## Minors and Children

We respect and recognize privacy interests related to children, and encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. Children under 13 (or under 16 in the European Economic Area) should not use our Site.

Back

* * *

## Changes

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

Back

* * *

## Contact Us

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us through the [contact page](https://www.freeppttemplates.com/feedback.html).
